module.exports = [
    {
        question: 'Located within the municipal boundaries of Kirkland Lake, Ontario, there lies the controversially named village of ...',
        solution: 'Swastika'
    },
    {
        question: 'Suffering from an extremely rare side effect after getting hip surgery in 2010, a Dutch man has alienated his family because he cannot stop ...',
        solution: 'laughing'
    },
    {
        question: 'According to Forbes, the average income for an “ice cream taster” is $... a year.',
        solution: '56000'
    },
    {
        question: 'For one day in 1998, Topeka, Kansas renamed itself ...',
        solution: 'ToPikachu'
    },
    {
        question: 'A group known as the “Robin Hooders” in Keene, New Hampshire pay for other people’s ...',
        solution: 'parking meters'
    },
    {
        question: 'On November 12, 1970, George Thornton, a highway engineer in Oregon, had the unusual job of blowing up a ...',
        solution: 'dead whale'
    },
    {
        question: 'For a story he was reporting on in 1955, Dan Rather tried ... for the first time.',
        solution: 'heroin'
    },
    {
        question: 'On November 25, 2013, a 16-month-old Chinese girl underwent surgery to remove the unusual growth of a ... in her ear canal.',
        solution: 'dandelion'
    },
    {
        question: 'Tara Reid once said, “I make Jessica Simpson look like a ... scientist.”',
        solution: 'rock'
    },
    {
        question: 'The rare condition known as “argyria” causes people’s skin to ...',
        solution: 'turn blue'
    }
]
